<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<wrapFeed>
<Job>
<JobId>2008-26819</JobId>
<ApplyUrl>http://jobs-fedexkinkos.icims.com/fedexkinkos_jobs/jobs/candidate/job.jsp?jobid=26819&amp;mode=view</ApplyUrl>
<JobCategory>Retail Center</JobCategory>
<JobTitle>Center Customer Service Coord</JobTitle>
<JobRegion>Southeast Region 47</JobRegion>
<JobDescription> Apply now!  &amp;bull; High school diploma or equivalent, plus six months to one year of related experience required &amp;bull; Excellent verbal and written communication skills &amp;bull; Physical stamina sufficient to stand during entire shift, excluding rest breaks &amp;bull; Physical stamina sufficient to move and lift 55 pound boxes &amp;bull; Ability, on a consistent basis, to perform work activities requiring cooperation, instruction, persuasion, or speaking with others &amp;bull; Ability, on a consistent basis, to maintain attention and concentration for extended periods of time &amp;bull; Ability, on a consistent basis, to function in a high stress environment, under substantial time pressure &amp;bull; Ability to work with minimal supervision &amp;bull; Ability to lead and direct team members &amp;bull; Ability to perform the General Duties and Responsibilities set forth above in a consistent and efficient manner   Benefits Website This is a representative list of the general duties the Customer Service Coordinator may be asked to perform and is not intended to be all-inclusive  &amp;bull; Provides customer service, including anticipating customer needs, suggesting alternatives and problem solving, and is able to satisfy those needs with a minimum amount of supervision &amp;bull; Takes customer orders, giving pricing information, performs consultative selling to customers, and explains the benefits of digital printing technology to customers &amp;bull; Sets priorities of customer projects &amp;bull; Follows copying protocol (copyright law, confidentiality, and careful handling of original documents) &amp;bull; Handles customer issues and gives refunds &amp;bull; May provide leadership on assigned shifts &amp;bull; May assist team members in goal setting and skill development &amp;bull; Assists in the training of center team members &amp;bull; Performs multiple tasks at the same time, using automatic equipment capabilities &amp;bull; Troubleshoots routine equipment problems &amp;bull; May pick-up and deliver customer orders &amp;bull; Collates, sorts and organizes customer orders &amp;bull; May operate photocopy, binding and other auxiliary equipment &amp;bull; Operates the Point of Sale terminal (POS), handles money and makes change. &amp;bull; Performs daily close-out procedures on POS. &amp;bull; Prepares bank deposit slips &amp;bull; Performs administrative duties, including bidding, ordering supplies and inventory control &amp;bull; Follows instructions of supervisors and assists other team members in performing center functions &amp;bull; Perform all other duties as needed or requested &amp;bull; Secondary responsibility for coordination of all shipping related services and activities, to include: &amp;bull; Provides customer service by determining appropriate shipping methods, informing customers of company products, services, routes, and rates.  &amp;bull; Ensures quality customer service is given to customers by providing packaging services, as well as offering information about company products and services. &amp;bull; Offer assistance to customers by suggesting appropriate shipping methods. Maintains inventory of shipping supplies. &amp;bull; Maintains log of all incoming and outgoing parcels, prepares parcels for pickup by delivery drivers, and sorts incoming parcels. &amp;bull; Assembles parcels and prepares goods for shipping by wrapping items in insulation, inserting items into shipping containers, weighing packages, and affixing labels to parcels. &amp;bull; Directs work of other team members. Performs duties with only minimal supervision by center manager and/or assistant manager. Must defer decisions involving changes in center procedures to center manager and/or assistant manager. This team member is required to perform many functions within the center, including all functions performed by Customer Service Associate team members. Additionally, this team member will perform functions such as purchasing, scheduling, problem solving, setting up new customer accounts, preparing bank deposits, and directing team members in one or more major function areas, to include Express Services and Computer Services. &amp;nbsp;</JobDescription>
<JobType>Regular Part-Time</JobType>
<JobCity>Miami</JobCity>
<JobState>FL</JobState>
<JobZip>33139</JobZip>
</Job>
<Job>
<JobId>2008-27771</JobId>
<ApplyUrl>http://jobs-fedexkinkos.icims.com/fedexkinkos_jobs/jobs/candidate/job.jsp?jobid=27771&amp;mode=view</ApplyUrl>
<JobCategory>Retail Center</JobCategory>
<JobTitle>Center Manager, Standalone</JobTitle>
<JobRegion>Northeast Region 54</JobRegion>
<JobDescription> Primarily respon<![CDATA[sible for managing the overal]]>l center operation, including supervision of team members and the administration of center sales performance and profitability objectives  &amp;bull; 4 year college degree, or equivalent level of experience &amp;bull; Three to five years of related experience, including one to three years of prior progressively responsible supervisory experience &amp;bull; Advanced level of reading, writing and mathematical ability &amp;bull; Proven ability to communicate effectively with team members and customers &amp;bull; Proven ability to lead, direct and supervise &amp;nbsp; This is a representative list of the general duties the Center Manager (Stand Alone) may be asked to perform and is not intended to be all-inclusive &amp;bull; Achieve center objectives for sales and profit performance &amp;bull; Direct supervision of team members, including responsibility for: &amp;bull; Hiring of all team members and monitoring new hire orientation procedures &amp;bull; Train and evaluate the efficiency and productivity of team members by establishing performance standards and objectives; conducting regular Operations Reviews and Performance Appraisals and making recommendations for wage increases and promotions, when applicable &amp;bull; Initiate disciplinary procedures, as necessary, for team members, up to and including termination of employment &amp;bull; Participate in the Complaint Review process as immediate supervisor of team members &amp;bull; Ensure the maintenance of fiscal reporting procedures within center, including accounts receivables, inventory reports, daily sales recaps, and daily bank deposits in full compliance with established company policies &amp;bull; Monitor and direct marketing activities within center to achieve pre-established sales objectives including monthly marketing calendars, media advertising, specialized sales, in-store signage, etc. &amp;bull; Plan and direct the purchase and installation of equipment and machinery required for efficient production operations and for monitoring inventory levels of supplies and materials  &amp;bull; Ensure Federal/State Law safety requirements are established within center. In addition, may be required to perform quarterly safety inspections of center. &amp;bull; Ensure team members within center are consistently applying FedEx Kinko&amp;#39;s Policies and Procedures. Apply now!</JobDescription>
<JobType>Regular Full-Time</JobType>
<JobCity>Norwood</JobCity>
<JobState>MA</JobState>
<JobZip>02062</JobZip>
</Job>
<Job>
<JobId>2008-25646</JobId>
<ApplyUrl>http://jobs-fedexkinkos.icims.com/fedexkinkos_jobs/jobs/candidate/job.jsp?jobid=25646&amp;mode=view</ApplyUrl>
<JobCategory>Retail Center</JobCategory>
<JobTitle>Center Specialist - S &amp; G</JobTitle>
<JobRegion>Heartland Region 35</JobRegion>
<JobDescription> &amp;nbsp;  Apply now! High school diploma or equivalent, plus one to three years of specialized (sign production) experience  Entry level experience in design or graphics software   Excellent verbal and written communication skills  Proficient at craftsmanship type work  Possesses a strong attention to detail  Extremely organized  Able to manage multiple projects simultaneously  Able to work with minimal supervision  Ability to lead and direct team members  Excellent computer skills  Basic knowledge of Adobe software applications  Physical stamina sufficient to stand during entire shift, excluding rest breaks  Physical stamina sufficient to move and lift 55 pound boxes  Ability, on a consistent basis, to communicate effectively with team members and customers  Ability, on a consistent basis, to maintain attention and concentration for extended periods of time  Ability, on a consistent basis, to function in a high stress environment under substantial time pressure  Ability to perform the General Duties and Responsibilities set forth above in a consistent and efficient manner This is a representative list of the general duties the Signs &amp;amp; Graphics Specialist may be asked to perform and is not intended to be all inclusive. &amp;bull; Monitors Signs &amp;amp; Graphics machine performance and conducts machine maintenance as required. &amp;bull; Fills out and tracks service logs for machines and communicates with vendor. &amp;bull; Takes preemptive action to prevent errors and waste. &amp;bull; May manage production workflow. &amp;bull; May maintain and purchase supplies. &amp;bull; Provide customer service including anticipating customer needs, suggesting alternatives and problem solving and is able to satisfy those needs with a minimum amount of supervision. &amp;bull; Takes customer orders, giving pricing information, performs consultative selling to customers and explains the benefits of different sign types based on production and pricing knowledge. &amp;bull; Assists in the training of center team members (may also include training team members from other centers). &amp;bull; Tenders customer orders using the OTP (Order To Pay) system. &amp;bull; Works with other centers to ensure that Signs &amp;amp; Graphics orders are shared correctly in the OTP (Order To Pay) system. &amp;bull; Stays up to date on all Signs &amp;amp; Graphics merchandising materials and FKSO communications regarding Signs &amp;amp; Graphics and is responsible for executing Signs &amp;amp; Graphics programs in the center.   &amp;nbsp;  May direct work of other team members. Performs duties with only minimal supervision by center manager and/or assistant manager. Must defer decisions involving changes in center procedures to center manager and/or assistant manager. This team member&amp;#39;s primary responsibilities include producing complex orders and operating large format equipment that requires more advanced knowledge and expertise. This team member will assist the Assistant Manager, Signs &amp;amp; Graphics in managing, monitoring, and facilitating all Signs &amp;amp; Graphics systems and production processes. This team member may manage the tracking process, coordinate production, coordinate pick-ups and deliveries, perform final quality checks and ensure communication among shifts. In addition, this position communicates with other team members and/or customers as needed during production and oversees job sharing with other FedEx Kinko&amp;#39;s locations and outside vendors. This team member will be responsible for taking customer orders and consulting with the customer regarding their order.</JobDescription>
<JobType>Regular Full-Time</JobType>
<JobCity>Columbia</JobCity>
<JobState>MO</JobState>
<JobZip>65201</JobZip>
</Job>
<Job foo="bar" max="mammel" />
<Job>
<JobId>2008-27792</JobId>
<ApplyUrl>http://jobs-fedexkinkos.icims.com/fedexkinkos_jobs/jobs/candidate/job.jsp?jobid=27792&amp;mode=view</ApplyUrl>
<JobCategory>Retail Center</JobCategory>
<JobTitle>Center Customer Service Assoc</JobTitle>
<JobRegion>Heartland Region 35</JobRegion>
<JobDescription>  High school level of reading, writing and mathematical ability. High school diploma or equivalent preferred.   Good verbal and written communication skills   Physical stamina sufficient to stand during entire shift, excluding rest breaks   Physical stamina sufficient to move and lift 55 pound boxes   Ability, on a consistent basis, to communicate effectively with team members and customers   Ability, on a consistent basis, to perform work activities requiring cooperation, instruction, persuasion, or speaking with others   Ability, on a consistent basis, to maintain attention and concentration for extended periods of time   Ability, on a consistent basis, to function in a high stress environment, under substantial time pressure   Ability to perform the General Duties and Responsibilities set forth above in a consistent and efficient manner     Benefits Website Apply now! This team member is required to perform many functions within the center, including, but not limited to, operating a wide variety of equipment, taking customer orders, assisting customers, moving boxes and equipment, operating computers and computerized equipment, writing and filling out forms, sorting and collating papers, handling money, following instructions from supervisors, and communicating effectively with other team members. In some centers, the team member may work in the back office, photo lab, mail center, or business services department. Additionally, this team member may drive a motor vehicle, order products from catalogs, learn advanced computer software applications, and perform various administrative functions. &amp;nbsp; This is a representative list of the general duties the Customer Service Associate may be asked to perform and is not intended to be all-inclusive    Provides customer service, including anticipating customer needs, suggesting alternatives and problem solving, and is able to satisfy those needs with a minimum amount of supervision   Takes customer orders, giving pricing information, performs consultative selling to customers, and explains the benefits of digital printing technology to customers   Performs multiple tasks at the same time, using automatic equipment capabilities   Troubleshoots routine equipment problems   May assist in the training of center team members   May pick-up and deliver customer orders   Collates, sorts and organizes customer orders   Sets priorities of customer projects   May log orders in tracking system, perform quality checks, package, store, retrieve, and ring up orders (Production Tracking Process or PTP)   Operates photocopy, binding and other auxiliary equipment   Operates the Point of Sale terminal (POS), handles money and makes change.   Follows copying protocol (copyright law, confidentiality, and careful handling of original documents)   Follows instructions of supervisors and assists other team members in performing center functions   May assist with financial reporting, including daily sales, purchasing, center assets and payroll   May prepare bank deposits and purchase orders   May research customer account problems to resolve disputes   May coordinate asset moves with KFSO   May maintain filing system   May ensure center has necessary supplies, equipment and inventory   May generate POS reports as needed   May input waste tracking data and generate reports   Perform all other duties as needed or requested   Secondary responsibility for coordination of all shipping related services and activities, to include:   Provides customer service by determining appropriate shipping methods, informing customers of company products, services, routes, and rates.   Ensures quality customer service is given to customers by providing packaging services, as well as offering information about company products and services.   Offer assistance to customers by suggesting appropriate shippin<!-- this is a comment with CDATA in it <![CDATA[ <xml><tags></tags></xml> ]]> -->g methods. Maintains inventory of shipping supplies.   Maintains log of all incoming and<!-- this is a comment. --> outgoing parcels, prepares parcels for pickup by delivery drivers, and sorts incoming parcels.   Assem<![CDATA[checked peri<some><test><tags>Inside of <!--some CDATA</tags></test>odically.--> Authority is limited ]]>bles parcels and prepares goods for shipping by wrapping items in insulation, inserting items into shipping containers, weighing packages, and affixing labels to parcels.   Must follow instructions of supervisors. Duties are performed with limited supervision. Accuracy of work is <![CDATA[checked peri<some><test><tags>Inside of some CDATA</tags></test>odically. Authority is limited ]]>as directed by supervisors.</JobDescription>
<JobType>Regular Part-Time</JobType>
<JobCity>Wichita</JobCity>
<JobState>KS</JobState>
<JobZip>67226</JobZip>
</Job>
</wrapFeed>
